Now, we should be able to figure out the most
appropriate URL that our app should use. Based on the
UX wireframes that we saw earlier, you noticed that we'll
want one week's worth of data. For this quiz and for
the example code that I'll be showing you later, we're
going to be using the postal code for Mountain View which is
94043. By all means, you should use your own location
either specifying the postal code, city name or the latitude, longitude
coordinates. Next we want their format from the server to be in JSON format,
and we want the units to be reported in metric. But our UI will
be able to display Celsius or Fahrenheit
based on user preferences, and we'll just
do the conversion ourself. Enter the URL
that fulfills these requirements in the box below,